mypleasure.com 2013-10-23

# Privacy Policy & Security -- MyPleasure.com

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.mypleasure.com&sealid=101) MyPleasure.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this web site has agreed to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the web site 
  2. The organization collecting the information 
  3. How the information is used 
  4. With whom the information may be shared 
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under MyPleasure.com control 
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the MyPleasure Privacy Team by email at [privacy@mypleasure.com](mailto:privacy@mypleasure.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
MyPleasure.com will not share, sell or rent this information to others in any way other than as disclosed in this policy or stated at the point where the information is collected. MyPleasure.com collects information from our users in several areas of our Web site as described in this privacy policy. 

**Order Forms**  
We request information from you on our order form, including your contact information (such as name, email and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). This information is used to fill your orders and for billing and shipping purposes. If we have trouble processing your order, we may use this contact information to get in touch with you. We share this information, and only that information that we believe is necessary, with those third parties that are involved in the processing of your order. For example, the financial institution that issued your credit card, and the shipping carrier that delivers your order. However, we never actually store your credit card in our database. It is discarded the moment your card is authorized. 

**Product Reviews**  
If you choose to participate in submitting product reviews on our website, we may ask you for information, including your email address, age, gender and online name. All reviews are reviewed and edited prior to posting. If your review is accepted, we will post your online name, rating and age as well as your actual review. Generally, we use this information to improve our site and product selection and as a resource for other visitors. 

**Polls**  
Our optional online surveys may ask visitors for demographic information (such as relationship status) to help us better understand our customers in aggregate. This information is not linked to any other personal or identifying information. 

**Tell a Friend**  
If you elect to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site, we ask for your name and email address as well as that of your friend. We automatically send your friend and you a one-time email inviting him or her to visit our site. We store this information indefinitely for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. You or your friend may contact us at [remove@MyPleasure.com](mailto:remove@MyPleasure.com) to request removal of this information from our database. 

If you contact MyPleasure via email regarding any matter, you will not be contacted for any reason other than as a response to the question or feedback. You will not be defaulted into receiving any promotional material simply by contacting us. 

**Postcards**  
If you elect to use our postcard service to send a message, we will add your email address to our database. We may send you special offers from time to time. You may contact us at [remove@MyPleasure.com](mailto:remove@MyPleasure.com) to request removal of this information from our database. 

**Newsletter**  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as your name and e-mail address. Subscription to our newsletter is optional and requires your consent via our newsletter subscription form. Unsubscribe instructions are included with the newsletter. 

**Special Offers**  
When you check the "opt-in" box on the order page, you may occasionally receive information on products, services and special deals. We offer you the option to discontinue receiving these communications by "opting out" of receiving promotional offers and material. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a message that the server for our Web site gives to your Web browser. Your browser stores the message in a file called cookie.txt. Each time the browser requests a page from the server, a message is sent back to the server. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. The next time you visit our site, your browser will send the cookie to the server, which can use the information to present you with a more personalized experience (such as retaining the contents of your shopping basket). MyPleasure uses cookies for only two purposes: to maintain your shopping basket and to track which ad you clicked to get to our site. We do not use cookies to store passwords or any personal information about you. 

If you reject the cookie, you may still use our site; however, the contents of your shopping basket will not be retained between visits. 

**Session ID**  
Upon visiting our site, we assign you a unique Session ID and attempt to store that onto your computer in the form of a cookie. This is used to keep track of your shopping basket during your visit and between visits. 

**Affiliate ID**  
If you entered our site by clicking a link on one of our affiliate Web sites, we will attempt to store the ID of the affiliate as a cookie. We do this to ensure the affiliate receives proper credit for any subsequent order you might place. Your personally identifiable information will not be shared with any affiliates. 

**Log Files**  
We use standard server log files to identify IP addresses, browser type, domain name, date and time users have accessed MyPleasure.com. We use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track a user's movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. "Aggregate use" means that information from all users is collected and gathered into a whole unit so that information as a whole can be used. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
As all other retail stores, we use a credit card processing merchant bank to bill users for goods and services. This company is contractually obligated to not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We have partnerships with other companies and individuals to provide specific services. If you sign up for these services, we will share your name or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Aside from the previously mentioned third parties involved in the processing of your order, we do not share your personally identifiable information with any other entities. We also may disclose your information to a third party if we believe in good faith that the law or legal process requires it, to protect the rights or property of MyPleasure.com or others, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy. 

**Your Choice to Opt-Out**  
You have the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask you for the information. For example, our order form has an opt-out box. If you want to buy a product from us, but you do not want to receive future promotional e-mails, you simply uncheck the box to opt-out of the group receiving such e-mails. 

If you no longer wish to receive promotional e-mails from us or from our partners, you may opt-out clicking on the unsubscribe link within any email we send you. 

We notify you when your information is being collected by any outside parties. You may then make an informed choice as to whether or not you would like to continue receiving services that require an outside party. 

 Occasionally, we may work with third parties in sending promotional emails or newsletters. In such cases, we may provide our opt-out list to the third-party for the limited purpose of removing those email addresses from the mailing.

**Correcting and Updating Personal Information**  
If any of your personally identifiable information or email address changes, or if you no longer wish to use our service, we offer you a way to correct, update or remove your personal data that you have provided to us. This can be done by e-mailing us at [customerservice@MyPleasure.com](mailto:customerservice@MyPleasure.com). 

**Security**  
We want to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information on our Web site, we take commercially reasonable steps to protect your information online and off-line. 

When you provide sensitive information on our site (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and protected with encryption software while in transit. While you are on a secure page, such as our order form page, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked. 

While we use encryption software to protect sensitive information online, we also use our best efforts to protect your information off-line. Access to all of our users' information is restricted in our offices. We take reasonable steps to ensure that only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment behind a locked cage. 

We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting your credit card information during our online checkout process. In addition, we utilize the same encryption standard when transferring your credit card data to our internal fulfillment system. To further enhance our security measures, our fulfillment system is protected from access via the Internet and we we never store your actual credit card information. 

If you have any questions about the security for our Web site, please e-mail us at [security@MyPleasure.com](mailto:security@MyPleasure.com). 

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy or email practices, we will post a link to those changes on our Home Page so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by e-mail. You will have the choice to allow us to use the information in this different manner. We will use information according to the privacy policy posted at the time the information was collected, unless you agree otherwise. 

**Special Note for International Users**  
By visiting our Web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in our Privacy Policy. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data. 

**_Glossary of Terms_**

 **Affiliates**  
Affiliates are other Web sites that have agreed to place a MyPleasure link or ad on their site in return for percentage-based compensation for all orders that originate from their site. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file that many Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk, determine your email address, or read cookie files created by other sites. If you wish to prevent Web sites from setting cookies on your browser, you may set your browser to refuse cookies or to warn you before setting a cookie. 

**IP Address**  
When you are connected to the Internet, your computer has a unique Internet ID called an IP address. Most people that connect through a dial-up service, such as America Online, get a different IP address each time they login. Others might have a permanently assigned IP address, called a static IP address. It is difficult or impossible for a Web site to collect personal information about you (i.e., your name, email address, etc.) from your IP address alone, though it is easier if you have a static IP address. 

**Session ID**  
A unique ID assigned each time someone visits an online store with a shopping basket system. Each store you visit will assign you a different ID. Many stores use a cookie to save your Session ID for re-use when you return to that same store. Most shoppers find it convenient that their shopping basket is maintained between visits but others find it objectionable and therefore turn cookies off. 

**SSL Encryption**  
A method by which information transmitted across the Internet is scrambled to the point where it's hard to decipher by anyone who should intercept the data before it reaches its destination. Most reputable online stores make use of SSL encryption to request credit card information and other sensitive data from their customers. Web pages where SSL encryption is activated are typically identified by a lock or key symbol displayed somewhere in your browser. Refer to your browser's documentation for the specific symbol and location. 

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, wish to have information about you deleted, opt-out of mailings, or want to place an order via a method other than the Internet, you can contact us at: 

MyPleasure.com  
Sawhorse Enterprises  
1196 Cherry Avenue  
San Bruno, CA 94066 

Email: [info@mypleasure.com](mailto:info@mypleasure.com)  
Phone: 1-866-MYPLEASURE  
Fax: 650-873-8368 

**Policy last updated on: September 10, 2009**
